(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
3D Redebut Live Déjàvu
3D: March 26th, 2026 @studio. "DONT GET LOST AGAIN -kchan"
Hmmm...
Am I lost again?
This door looks sus.
Should I?
Or should I not?
Dahlah.
Oh well.
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Walk it off and go
Isn't this a thing that you're used to?
Disappointed and feeling blue
When the world doesn't go the way you want it to?
Oh oh
And maybe now is just the perfect time
To let it go and just unwind
There's no need to ask why ever again
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
What else can you do?
When your feelings are barely there
Up to a point of pure despair
When you have given it your all
but ends in vain
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Let life takes over the wheel
And shift it to higher gears
Then you will finally see
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
You don't need to be sad
You don't need to be mad
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes to get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja
Let it go
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, let it go
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
Let it go
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, let it go
Walk it off and go
ma ii ka
Oh well...
Podcast sendiri, ya? ソロポッドキャストってこと？
A solo podcast, huh?
Kaelooo~!
Nani?
What?
Apaan, tuh?
What's that?
9 lampu...
9 lights...
Mic...
headset...
Content creator?
Eh...
Warnanya...
The colors...
hololive ID!?
Sahabat sejatiku
My true friend
Hilangkah dari ingatanmu?
Have you forgotten in your memory?
Di hari kita
On the day we
saling berbagi
shared with each other
Dengan kotak sejuta mimpi
With a box of a million dreams
Aku datang menghampirimu
I came to approach you
Kuperlihatkan
To show you
semua hartaku
all my treasures
Kita slalu berpendapat
We always agreed
Kita ini yang terhebat
That we are the greatest
Kesombongan di masa
The arrogance of our
muda yang indah
beautiful youth
Aku raja, kau pun raja
I am the king, you are the king
Aku hitam, kau pun hitam
I am black, you are black
Arti teman lebih dari sekedar materi
The meaning of a friend is more than just material things
Pegang pundakku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold my shoulder, never let go
Bila ku mulai lelah
When I begin to tire
Lelah dan tak bersinar
Tired and not shining
Remas sayapku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Squeeze my wings, never let go
Okay, that's kind of an easy trick.
So that's how these rooms work, huh?
I guess this door is locked too, right?
Okay.
I need to find a clue here and get out.
Hmm...
OPEN THIS
[Text: OPEN THIS]
ONLY FOR THE WEAK ONES
[Text: ONLY FOR THE WEAK ONES]
What am I supposed to do with this?
Coffee? Arrow, right? What?
What's that mean?
What does that mean?
Hmm...
There's another box, but I'm not the weak one, so...
I have no idea.
Anyway, who's gonna judge me if I open the next clue? I just need to get out from here and leave this weird place...
...or else I'll be late for my 3D showcase.
Lompat, jalan kiri. Oke, ya udah, sana.
Jump, go left. Okay, fine, go there.
Oke, satu, dua, tiga, lompat! Jalan, kiri.
Okay, one, two, three, jump! Walk, left.
Lompat, jalan, kanan. Kenapa pula kau melompat?
Jump, walk, right. Why did you jump?
Lompat, kiri lagi.
Jump, left again.
Lompat! Enggak, oh, ini yang penting bisa, ya.
Jump! No, oh, the important thing is this works.
Kiri, kiri, kiri! Kiri! Kiri!
Left, left, left! Left! Left!
Eh?
I don't get it.
Oh! Kopikanan?
Oh! Kopikanan? (Copyright?)
Oh my...
What kind of clue is that?
Matahari terbenam
The sun sets
Temani dalam kesendirianku
Accompany me in my loneliness
Temani aku dalam kepedihan ini
Accompany me in this pain
Ini ku bertahan
As I endure this
Matahari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri jalan baru untuk hidupku
Giving a new path for my life
Ini ku bertahan
As I endure this
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can surely do it
Matahari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri jalan baru untuk hidupku
Giving a new path for my life
Ini ku bertahan
As I endure this
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can surely do it
Aku pasti bisa
I can surely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I am sure I can surely do it
Aku ingin lepaskan seluruh bebanku
I want to release all my burdens
Dan kujalani hidupku...
And live my life...
dengan senyuman...
...with a smile.
Aku pasti bisa.
I can definitely do it.
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya.
Enjoy it all and face it.
Aku yakin pasti bisa.
I am sure I can definitely do it.
Dan ku jalani hidupku dengan senyuman.
And I'll live my life with a smile.
Hahaha!
Oh... This room is... different?
Eh? Hobby? Sleeping.
Does this thing know if I lie? Whatever. Sleeping.
Ah, stop asking me the same question. Sleeping. I love sleeping.
Is this some kind of joke? My hobby is anything except answering the same questions over and over again.
Can the door just please open? I've had enough of this.
No, I refuse to answer.
Ah, whatever.
Oh! Finally a different one, and an easy one too! Eight! Tentu aja eight! Of course, eight!
Oh! Finally a different one, and an easy one too! Eight! Of course eight! Of course, eight!
広い宇宙の数ある一つ
One of many in this wide universe,
青い地球の広い世界で
in the great world of this blue earth...
小さな恋の思いは届く
This tiny feeling of love will reach you,
小さな島のあなたのもとへ
on the little island, to where you are.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Since we met, time has been flowing,
思いを込めた手紙も増える
the letters filled with my feelings grow in number.
いつしか二人互いに響く
Before we knew it, we are echoing between each other,
時に激しく 時に切なく
sometimes intensely, sometimes sadly.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Echoing distantly, to far, far away,
優しい歌は世界を変える
this gentle song changes the world.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the more important someone is to you...
すぐそばにいるの
...the closer they are to you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you, and only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
ほら
Look...
ほら...
響け恋 of 歌
Let this love song echo!
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You notice that we walk together,
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
even on dark roads, the moon shines on us daily.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Never letting go of our tightly held hands,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
my feelings are strong, swearing for eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
From the depths of eternity, I'm sure I'll say,
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
the same words, with my feelings unchanged.
それでも足りず
Even that won't be enough...
涙に変わり
...so they turn to tears...
喜びになり
...and become joy...
言葉にできず
...unable to speak...
ただ抱きしめる
...I just hold you close.
I just hold you close.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the more important someone is to you...
すぐそばにいるの
...the closer they are to you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you, and only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
ほら
Look...
ほら...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
夢ならば覚めないで
If this is a dream, please don't wake me up,
if this is a dream, please don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時
The time I spent with you...
永遠の星となる
...will become an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the more important someone is to you...
すぐそばにいるの
...the closer they are to you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you, and only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
響け恋の歌 ほら
Resound, song of love, look!
あなたにとって
To you,
大事な人ほど
the more important someone is,
すぐそばにいるの
the closer they are.
ただ あなたにだけ
I just want...
届いて欲しい
it to reach you...
響け恋の歌 ほら
Resound, song of love, look!
ほら
Look...
響け恋の歌
Resound, song of love!
REPEAT AFTER ME 10 TIMES
Eh? Ngulang apaan?
Eh? Repeat what?
Chaos?
Kepalaku emang lagi chaos sih, tapi maksudnya?
My mind is indeed chaotic, but what does it mean?
Meja murid ada lima, terus meja guru ada satu...
There are five student tables and one teacher table...
Aku nggak paham.
I don't get it.
Hmm... chaos.
Eh?
Hakoz Baelz?!
Jangan-jangan maksudnya itu?
Could it mean that?
JDONNN MY SOULLL!!!
JDON MY SOUL!!!
Kok pintunya nggak kebuka?
Why won't the door open?
Oh! Sepuluh kali!
Oh! Ten times!
Oke.
Okay.
JDON MY SOUL sepuluh kali!
JDON MY SOUL, ten times!
Eh, kayaknya bukan gitu, deh.
Eh, I guess it's not like that.
Jdon my soul! Jdon my soul! Jdon my soul! Jdon my soul! Jdon my soul!
Nice.
Wanna be the biggest dreamer
全速力で未来も現在も 駆け抜けろ
Run through the future and the present at full speed!
そう僕は気づいたんだ
Yes, I noticed
ずっと宿題 忘れてた
I'd forgotten my homework for the longest time
それはひとつの謎 謎 謎
It's one of those mysteries, mysteries, mysteries
「僕は誰なんだろう？」
“Who am I?”
スライディングして すりむけたヒザ
My knees are scraped from sliding
痛くたってね
Even if it hurts...
すぐ立ち上がらなきゃ
...I have to stand up immediately...
チャンスは逃げてゆく 分かってるさ
...or else the chance will slip away, I know that
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
夢見るコトが すべてはじまり
Dreaming is the start of everything...
それが答えだろ
...that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ 飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly further than anyone else...
すべての明日を貫いて
...piercing through all our tomorrows!
地平線まで 飛んでゆけ
Fly all the way to the horizon...
羽をもらった勇気たち
...those of us who were given wings of courage!
強く大きくなるために
To become stronger and bigger...
僕も走りだそう
...I will start running too!
聞こえていたよ カウントダウン
I've been hearing the countdown... quit it.
ずっと前から
...for the longest time
準備はできてるさ 今すぐはじめよう
I'm ready, let's start now...
ゼロに変われ！
...and turn to zero!
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
信じられなきゃ 瞬きしてる
If you don't believe, in the blink of an eye...
セツナに消えるよ
...it'll disappear in an instant!
ココロの標的 そらさず走れ
Run without taking your eyes off your heart's target...
すべてのチカラぶつけよう
...let's throw in all of our power!
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
夢見るコトが すべてはじまり
Dreaming is the start of everything......
それが答えだろ
...that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ 飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly further than anyone else...
すべての明日を貫いて
...piercing through all our tomorrows!
Bigger, bigger, biggest dreamer! 夢見る ことが すべて 始まり
Bigger, bigger, biggest dreamer! Dreaming is where everything begins
それが 答え だろう
That must be the answer
誰より 遠くへ 飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly further than anyone else
すべての 明日を 貫いて
Piercing through all of tomorrow
Bigger, bigger, biggest dreamer! 夢見る ことが すべて 始まり
Bigger, bigger, biggest dreamer! Dreaming is where everything begins
それが 答え だろう
That must be the answer
Wanna be the biggest dreamer 全力で
Wanna be the biggest dreamer, with all my might
未来も 今も 駆け抜けろ
Run through both the future and the present!
A bomb now?
Buset, ini sih bener-bener udah keterlaluan.
Jeez, this is really getting out of hand.
Harusnya sekarang aku lagi 3D Showcase, tapi malah nyasar...
I'm supposed to be doing my 3D Showcase right now, but instead I got lost...
...kejebak di ruangan yang ada bomnya, terus disuruh mecahin kode morse.
...trapped in a room with a bomb, and now I have to crack a morse code?
Hari ini apes banget!
What a terrible day!
Terus ada hape juga?
And there's a phone too?
Aku harus ngapain? Telepon YAGOO terus bilang aku nyasar dan perlu bantuan?
What am I supposed to do? Call YAGOO and tell him I'm lost and need help?
Kayaknya aku tahu harus ngapain!
Wait, I think I know what to do!
Ha, halo?
H-hello?
Aku nyasar, kejebak, terus ada bom juga.
I'm lost, trapped, and there's a bomb here.
Apa?
What?
Kalau Zany nggak bisa mecahin kode morse, bisa mampus aku.
If you can't decode morse code, I'm a goner.
Hah?
Oke, garis titik garis, titik titik titik, titik garis, garis garis, garis garis garis, garis titik, garis titik garis garis, titik garis.
Okay, dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dash-dot, dash-dot-dash-dash, dot-dash.
C, A, A...
Cepetan! Bomnya mau meledak!
Hurry! The bomb is about to explode!
Bisa diulang lagi nggak?
Can you repeat that again?
Garis titik garis, titik titik titik, titik garis, garis garis, garis garis garis, garis titik, garis titik garis garis, titik garis.
Dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dash-dot, dash-dot-dash-dash, dot-dash.
M, O... N... uhm...
Chamon apaan coba?
What on earth is Chamon?
Jadi aku bisa mampus beneran.
So I'm really going to die.
Kayaknya yang terakhir Y... A...
I think the last ones are Y... A...
Chamonya?
Apaan itu?
What is that?
Aku nggak tahu kamu ngapain, tapi semoga berhasil!
I don't know what you're doing, but good luck!
Makasih! Bye!
Thanks! Bye!
Cha, chamonya... Chachamonya?
Chachamonya?
I really want to be with you, I really want to be with you
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear, so trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も 恐れないで
Trust me, don't fear anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth
ちゃんと聴こえている 君の心の声
I can clearly hear the voice of your heart
小さなアンサーへ 僕が耳をあててあげる
I will press my ear to your tiny answer
何度も伝えたい 君は一人じゃない
I want to tell you over and over, you are not alone
変わることのない 愛はきっとここにある
An unchanging love is surely right here
泣いてみればいい
You can try crying
頼ってみればいい
You can try relying on me
その全てを受け止めると決めた
I decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
Call me 一つになる
Call me, we will become one
Trust me この想い ほどけないから
Trust me, because these feelings won't unravel
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the baggage you hold
Trust me 降ろしてみればいい そう君のためにも 僕がいるんだ
Trust me, you can try setting it down, yes, for your sake, I am here
I really want to be with you, trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
どれほどの悲しみ 君は隠してたの
How much sadness were you hiding?
どれほどの想いを 胸に閉じ込めてきたの
How many feelings have you kept locked away in your heart?
痛みと引き換えに 手に入れた強さを
The strength you gained in exchange for pain
いつか優しさへ 君は変えていけるはず
You should be able to turn it into kindness someday
奪われたって
Even if it's stolen
壊されたって
Even if it's broken
大事なのは君らしくいること
What's important is that you stay true to yourself
I'm here たとえ世界が
I'm here, even if the world
Call me 終わるとしても
Call me, even if it comes to an end
Trust me 繋ぐ手は 離さないから My dear いつわりはない
Trust me, I won't let go of your hand, My dear, there are no lies
Trust me 未来へ歩き出そう
Trust me, let's start walking toward the future
そう 君のために僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'll be by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't be afraid of anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていてこの温もり
Just feel this warmth
いつまでもそばにいる forever
I'll always be by your side, forever
いつまでも離れない never ever
I'll never ever leave you
君がいれば whatever you do
If you're here, whatever you do
ねぇ僕に教えて whatever you say
Hey, tell me, whatever you say
辛いことあれば全て飲み込み
If there are hard times, swallow them all
もしそれでも無理ならば込み込み
And if it's still too much, take it all in
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear
世界敵に回しても trust me
Even if I turn the whole world into an enemy, trust me
Trust me
Baby
泣いてみればいい 頼ってみればいい
It's okay to cry, it's okay to rely on me
そのすべてを受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
Call me 一つになれる
Call me, we can become one
Trust me この思いほどけないから
Trust me, because these feelings will never come undone
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the burden you carry
Trust me 下ろしてみればいい
Trust me, you should try putting it down
そう 君のために僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'll be by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't be afraid of anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていてこの温もり
Just feel this warmth
With me もう払わないで
With me, don't brush me away
Give me 心を開いて
Give me, open your heart
Feel me すべてを伝えて
Feel me, convey everything
With me 言葉はいらない
With me, no words are needed
Give me 見つめ合えばいい
Give me, just gaze at each other
Feel me すべてを azukete
Feel me, leave everything to me
Hello? Anybody here?
Hello? Is anyone here?
Okay, I have played enough horror games, and I don't know why, but it reminds me of something similar.
Should I read this? Maybe?
何が目的ですか？ 何でいるんですか？
What is your purpose? Why are you here?
キレてますか？ 怒ってますか？
Are you angry? Are you mad?
ここにいていいですか？
Can I stay here?
戻ります。帰りましょうか？ 戻ろうか？
I'm returning. Shall we go back? Shall I return?
何すればいい？ 何か手伝いますか？
What should I do? Can I help with anything?
敵意はありますか？
Is there hostility?
何者ですか？ どこにいますか？ 近くにいますか？
Who are you? Where are you? Are you nearby?
出てきて！ アピールしてください！ もしもし？
Come out! Make yourself known! Hello?
Okay, that door looks similar to the entrance door. Is that the exit?
Or is that a trap?
Well, if this is a horror game, should I try to scream?
AAAAAAHHH!!!
Diam!
Quiet!
Eh?
そう 悲しみを優しさに
Yes, turn sadness into kindness
自分らしさを力に
Turn your true self into strength
迷いながらでもいい
It's okay to wander/lose your way
歩き出して
Keep walking forward
もう一回
One more time
誰かの期待にずっと応え
Always meeting someone else's expectations
褒められるのが好きなのですか？
Do you just love being praised?
鳴り止まぬブザー すり抜けても
Even if you slip through the endless buzzers
笑顔はいつでも素敵ですか？
Is your smile always wonderful?
始まりだけ...
Waking up dreaming...
夢見て起きる
...only of the beginning
そのサヨナラは いつか
That goodbye will someday...
いつか
...someday...
自分の腕で
...be held in your own arms
そう 大事なものはいつも
Yes, the important things are always...
形のないもの
...things without a shape
...ものだけ
...only those things,
手に入れても なくしても
Even if I obtain them or lose them,
気づかぬまま
without even noticing.
そうさ悲しみをやさしさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさをちからに
turn your uniqueness into strength.
迷いながらでもいい
It's fine to lose your way,
歩き出して
just start walking.
もう一回
One more time.
強がることであきらめて
By acting tough, you give up,
逃げ込む場所の狭さだけ
just focusing on the narrowness of your refuge.
自分を失い出すくらいなら
If you're going to lose yourself,
傷つきながらすべてをさらって
then take everything while getting hurt.
新しい風 味方に
With the new wind on your side,
見つけて
find it,
探しているんだ
I am searching.
いつか 青い鳥を
Someday, that bluebird.
そうさ大事なものはいつも
That's right, the important things are always
形のないものだけ
only the formless ones.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if you obtain them or lose them,
気づかぬまま
without even noticing.
そうさ悲しみをやさしさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさをちからに
turn your uniqueness into strength.
迷いながらでもいい
It's fine to lose your way,
歩き出して
just start walking.
涙の跡はなぜか
For some reason, the tear tracks
ふっきれてただ
are gone, and I've just moved on.
空に逃げるように
Like escaping into the sky,
自然なこと
it's so natural.
雨はあがった
The rain has stopped.
だから大事なものはいつも
That's why the important things are always
形のないものだけ
only the formless ones.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if you obtain them or lose them,
気づかぬまま
without even noticing.
そうさ悲しみをやさしさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさをちからに
turn your uniqueness into strength.
キミならきっとやれる
If it's you, you can surely do it,
信じていて
believe in yourself.
もう一回
One more time.
小さな頃には宝の地図が
When I was young, a treasure map
頭の中に浮かんでいて
floated inside my head,
いつでも捜した奇跡の場所
always searching for that place of miracles,
知らない誰かに負けないように
so I wouldn't lose to someone I didn't know.
今では
But now,
ほこりだらけの毎日
each day is covered in dust,
いつの日か
someday,
すべての
I'll just
時に身を任せるだけ
surrender myself to all of time.
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If the world were to change,
何も知らない頃の私に
to the me who didn't know anything,
連れていって
take me there,
思い出が色あせないよう
so my memories won't fade away.
小さな頃から歌を歌って
I've been singing since I was little,
夢見る心 温めてた
keeping my dreaming heart warm.
みんなで真似した 秘密のメロディ
The secret melody we all imitated together,
今度は遠くに聞こえるように
so that this time, it can be heard far away.
今では
But now...
ため息ついてばかりで
...I do nothing but sigh,
誰もまだ
and nobody yet...
本当の夢さえ掴めないまま
...can even grasp their true dreams.
もしも時代が戻るのなら
If only time could turn back,
涙を知った頃の私に
to the me when I first knew tears,
連れていって 切なさが
take me there, so that sadness...
追いつかないように
...won't be able to catch up.
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If only the world could change,
何も知らない頃の私に
to the me when I knew nothing at all,
連れていって 思い出が
take me there, so that my memories...
色褪せないように
...won't ever fade away.
連れていって 切なさが
Take me there, so that sadness...
追いつかないように
...won't be able to catch up.
Why does everything feel so real?
Am I real?
Can you even feel my existence?
Is this what déjà vu looks like?
All these memories...
...mean the world to me.
Thank you for walking...
...this journey with me.
Let's make more! :3
like! comments! share! subscribe!